A Guide to the Papers of the Stuart-Baldwin Families, 1764-1884
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- II: Legal and Financial Papers, including Miscellaneous Papers
  - Legal and Financial Papers - Wills (Copies): John Oliver (1791); Jacob Peck (1825); John W. Pheeters (1796); James Rowland (1834); George Skillern (n.d.); Samuel Sprouls (n.d.); Archibald Stuart (1829 & 1832) ca. 1791-1834 (Box 18)
  - Legal and Financial Papers - Miscellaneous Fragments ca. 1769-1802, n.d. (Box 18)
  - Membership Certificates of Alexander H.H. Stuart from the Virginia Historical Society 1881-1882 (Box 19)
  - Military Papers re the Continental Army and others 1779-1783, 1834, n.d. (Box 19)
  - Military Papers of Samuel Walker 1778 Aug 24-25 (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous Bound Volumes belonging to Alexander H.H. Stuart and Maggie B. Stuart 1773, ca. 1859, n.d. (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, including a dinner invitation, clippings, prayers, poems, and personal notes [1853] & n.d. (Box 19)
  - Notes concerning Lawyers and the Legal Profession n.d. (Box 19)
  - Notes concerning Rome and Roman History made by [Alexander H.H. Stuart ?] n.d. (Box 19)
  - Speeches - Drafts n.d. (Box 19)